<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="headingName">Beatles Anthology Vol. 1</string>
    <string name="leftContent">
        Behind That Locked Door: Beatles Rarities!
    </string>
    <string name="rightContent">
        In a vault deep inside in Abbey Road Studios in London - protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police alarmed door are something like
        400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the Let It Be
        album. The best of which are found on the Yellow Dog label. However, the best of the best were finally released by Apple Records in the
        form of the 3-volume Anthology series (at left) which offers out-takes and historical recordings that represent a milestone in classic
        rock. There are many interesting arrangements for songs that are much different than the released versions,
        and numerous "layered" out-takes demonstrating the various layers of overdubbing that was required for such experimentation
        when using the primitive 4-track equipment of that time.
This volume starts with the first "new" Beatle song, "Free as a Bird" (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on the bootleg ,AeuThe Lost
        LennonTapes Vol. 28,Aeu), and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from
        early concerts and BBC Radio sessions. In a vault deep inside in Abbey Road Studios in London - protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police alarmed door are something like
        400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the Let It Be
        album. The best of which are found on the Yellow Dog label. However, the best of the best were finally released by Apple Records in the
        form of the 3-volume Anthology series (at left) which offers out-takes and historical recordings that represent a milestone in classic
        rock. There are many interesting arrangements for songs that are much different than the released versions,
        and numerous "layered" out-takes demonstrating the various layers of overdubbing that was required for such experimentation
        when using the primitive 4-track equipment of that time.
This volume starts with the first "new" Beatle song, "Free as a Bird" (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on the bootleg ,AeuThe Lost
        LennonTapes Vol. 28,Aeu), and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from
        early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
    </string>
</resources>
